Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Sturges, Louise., 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Sturges, Louise., 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1927.; 3 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1929.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1929.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1930.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1930.; 14 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1931.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1931.; 6 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1932.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1932.; 7 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1933.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Sturges,,Solomon., 1933.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1933.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1933.; 15 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1934.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1934.; 17 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1935.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1935.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1935.; 6 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1936.; 14 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1937.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1937.; 12 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1937.; 9 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1938.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1938.; 10 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1938.; 13 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1938.; 17 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1939.; 11 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Sturges, Solomon., 1939.; 5 pieces. (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Sturges, Sol & Marie., 1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Sturges, Sot & Marie., 1950.; 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Sturges, Sot., n.d.; 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Sturges, Solomon II., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Sturges, Soloman II., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Sturges, Soloman II., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Sturges, Soloman II., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Sturges, Soloman II., 11 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Sturges, Soloman II., 17 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Ta - Ti., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Ta - Ti., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Ta - Ti., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Ta - Ti., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Ta - Ti., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Ta - Ti., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Ta - Ti., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Ta - Ti., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Ta - Ti., 14 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Tannen, Julius., 7 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Taylor, Valerie., 3 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Théry, Jacques., 1 piece. (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Tierney, Harry., 1 piece. (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - To - Tz., 11 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - To - Tz., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - To - Tz., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - To - Tz., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - To - Tz., 6 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Todd, Michael., 3 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Trainor, Alissa Keir., 11 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Trainor, Alissa.Keir., 7 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Transpacific Yacht Club., 14 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Trent, Philip., 3 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Trotti, Lamar., 4 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Truffaut, Francois., 4 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation - Zanuck., 12 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation - Zanuck., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation - Zanuck., 11 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation - Zanuck., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation - Zanuck., 10 pieces. (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - U., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder l)
  - U., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - U., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - United Artists Corporation., 3 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - United States Coast Guard., 4 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - United States Customs., 7 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - United States Government - Internal Revenue., 18 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - United States Government - Internal Revenue., 13 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - United States Marine Corp., 13 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - U.S. miscellaneous., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - U.S. miscellaneous., 6 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - U.S. - Veterans Administration., 8 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 23 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 26 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 11 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation., 14 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - V., 15 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - V., 11 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - V., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - V., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - V., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - V., 41 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - V., 11 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - V., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - V., 9 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Vallé, Rudy., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Vallé, Rudy., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Vallé, Rudy., 10 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Vallé, Rudy., 5 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Verdon, Gwen., 5 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Verneuil, Louis., 7 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Vidor, Charles., 1 piece. (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Vivian, Robert., 4 pieces. (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Von Stroheim, Erich., 1 piece. (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Wa., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Wa., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Wa., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Wa., 11 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Wa., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Walburn, Raymond., 3 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Wallace, William D., 8 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Wanger, Walter., 8 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Warner Brothers., 4 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Warrick, Ruth., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - We., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - We., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - We., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - We., 11 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - We., 18 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - We., 15 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Weiler, John., 17 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Welles, Orson., 6 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Wellman, William., 1 piece. (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Westside Asthma & Riding Club., 16 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Wh., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Wh., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Wh., 20 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - White, Gertrude (aunt-in-law)., 1 piece. (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Whitley, Marion., 5 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Wi., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Wi., 11 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Wi., 12 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Wi., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Wi., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Wi., 11 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Wilder, Billy., 1 piece. (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Winchell, Walter., 2 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Winkler, Daniel., 8 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - Winston, Archer., 1 piece. (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Wo - Wz., 12 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Wo - Wz., 12 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Wo - Wz., 10 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Wo - Wz., 15 pieces. (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Wolfson, Sonia., 9 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Wood, Peggy., 1 piece. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 11 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 12 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 11 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Woolfan, Bertrand E., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Wright, Frank L., 9 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Wyler, Robert., 3 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Wyler, William and Melanie., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Wynn, Ed., 6 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Y., 12 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Young, Loretta., 1 piece. (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - X., 1 piece. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Z., 12 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Zanuck, Darryl., 5 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Unknown., 13 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Unknown., 11 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Unknown., 10 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Unknown., 12 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Unknown., 11 pieces. (Box 89, Folder 26)
- Supplement
  Including production material, business and professional material, and correspondence.
  Arranged by Lilace Hatayama.
  - Child Of Manhattan (Play, Produced ), 1932
    - Budget., n.d.; 4 pieces. Holograph. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Casting inquiries. v.p., 1931-1932.; 29 pieces. Holograph and typescript. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence. v.p., 1931-1932.; 43 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Credits. n.p., n.d.; 1 piece. Holograph. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Notes. n.p., n.d.; 2 pieces. Holograph. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Production crew inquiries. v.p., 1932.; 13 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Programs. The Playgoer. season., 1931-1932; 5 pieces. Includes one complete copy of program, one incomplete copy, 3 leaves errata. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Script. Revised and discarded scenes., ca. 1931-1932.; 113 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Sets., ca. 1931-1932.; 45 pieces. Holograph and typescript. Includes sketches and notes. (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - The Great Moment., 1944
    - Correspondence., ca. 400 pieces. (Box 90, Folder 10-24)
      Correspondence is primarily from members of the Southern Medical Association recommending that proper credit be given to Dr. Crawford W. Long of Georgia as the discoverer of ether. Sturges' film credits W.T.G. Morton, a Bostonian dentist, as the discoverer of ether.
  - Hail The Conquering Hero., 1944
    - Budget., 1943.; 5 pieces. Typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Casting., 1943.; 13 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence. v.p., 1943-1944.; 19 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Dialogue., 1943.; 8 pieces. Typescript carbon with holograph corrections. (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Ephemera. Leatherneck lingo and I'm a marine., 2 items. (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Loan agreement., 1944.; 1 piece. Typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Memos., 1943.; 15 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Mobile unit plans. Diagrams., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Music., 1943.; 10 pieces. Holograph, typescript and mimeo. (Box 90, Folder 33)
      Includes recording program, lyrics and notes.
    - Publicity, v.p., 1945.; 14 pieces. Typescript, mimeograph and photostat. (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Purchase of story rights. Hollywood., 1943.; 1 piece. Photostatic copy. (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Strictly Dishonorable (Play, Produced ), 1929
    - Box office receipts., 1929-1931.; ca. 800 pieces. (Box 91, Folder 1-10)
      Includes New York and Chicago productions.
  - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences
    - Bulletins., 1934-1948.; 12 leaves. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence., 1941-1948.; 10 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Membership cards., 1945-1946.; 2 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Programs., 1945-1946.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - American National Theatre and Academy., ca. 1949-1950.; 7 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      Includes newsletters, description of ANTA and nomination for membership certificate.
  - Applications
    - Household help., 1947-1949.; 7 pieces. Holograph and mimeograph. (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Music and film scores., 1945-1946.; 24 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Publicity., 1945-1948.; 6 pieces. Typescript, typescript carbon and mimeograph. (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Translators and writers., 1939-1949.; 67 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Bowling., 1935-1938.; 36 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 10)
      Includes telegrams, scores, Bowler and Sports Review magazine (April 1938 issue).
    - Character actors. v.p., v.d.; 114 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 11-12)
    - Check stubs., 1936-1939.; 104 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Chemin de Fer Shoes., ca. 1937-1940
    - Accounts., 11 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 14)
      Includes account book labeled journal.
    - Cards., 13 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 15)
      These are mockups for a set of playing cards.
    - Certificate of Registry and Treasury Reports., 11 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence., ca. 1939-1940.; 12 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 17)
      Sturges' correspondence with the U.S. Treasury Department.
    - Orders., 7 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Printing and engraving., 22 pieces. (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Contracts., 1947-1952.; 56 pieces. Typescript, typescript carbon and mimeograph. (Box 93, Folder 1)
      Motion picture contracts with various studios, including MGM, Paramount and Twentieth Century-Fox.
    - Copyright., ca. 1927.; 11 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 2)
      For Rambling Along, words and music by Preston Sturges.
      Includes check, music, ephemera from the Library of Congress Copyright Office.
    - Cosmetic formulas. Preston Sturges & Company., ca. 1923.; 7 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Film economy proposals., 1942.; 2 items. Typescript carbon and mimeograph. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Film reviews. Brazil., 1940.; 1 piece. Typescript. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Form letters., 1943 and n.d.; 3 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Ideas., 1949.; 1 piece. Typescript. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Inventory., 1944.; 3 pieces. Typescript. (Box 93, Folder 8)
      Sturges' property at California Studios.
    - Keys., 6 items. (Box 93, Folder 9)
      Includes 2 keys and 4 envelopes with description.
    - Made in Hollywood., 1930-1931.; 4 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 10)
      Ephemera. Reviews of Brock Pemberton production.
    - Music. New York. The Girl from the Golden West., c. 1908.; 3 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - New York Trust Company. v.p. Correspondence and statements., v.d.; ca. 100 items. (Box 93, Folder 12-13)
    - Notes. v.p. The Outlaw. Howard Hughes production., v.d.; 12 pieces. Typescript and holograph. (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Ephemera., 1946.; 5 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 15)
      Reviews of The Outlaw.
    - Hughes Tool Company vs. Motion Picture Association of America, including re seal of approval for The Outlaw., 1946.; 18 pieces. Mimeograph. (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Itinerary., March 5, 1946.; 1 piece. Typescript. (Box 93, Folder 17)
      Publicity tour for Jane Russell and Jimmy Conlin.
    - Personnel. Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation., 1946-1947.; 30 pieces. Mimeograph. (Box 93, Folder 18)
      Includes list of contract players and technicians.
    - Petty cash vouchers., ca. 1946.; 2 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Pianos., 1929-1949.; 20 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 20)
      Includes correspondence, receipts, business cards.
  - The Players Restaurant, Los Angeles
    - Correspondence. v.p., v.d.; 80 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Finances., v.d.; 83 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 22)
      Includes memos and payroll ledger.
    - Receipts and invoices., 1948-1951.; 6 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Recipes., n.d.; 5 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - The Players Theatre, Los Angeles., ca. 1951
    - Advertising and publicity., 45 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 25)
      Includes advertising copy and printed samples of advertisements.
    - Contracts., 25 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence. v.p., v.d. ca. 1940. (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Ephemera., 19 pieces. (Box 93, Folder 28)
      Includes programs and tickets.
    - Introductory song., 3 pieces. Holograph and typescript. (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Production material., ca. 1951.; 49 pieces. Holograph, typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Production Managers' Guild., 1943.; 1 item. Printed. (Box 94, Folder 2)
      Credits bulletin.
    - Radio., ca. 1945.; 5 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence and advertising material.
  - Residence
    - Construction costs., 1951-1952.; 88 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 4)
      Invoices and correspondences.
    - Relocation of house., 1951.; 78 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, insurance, invoices.
    - Repairs. Invoices., 1937.; 67 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Screen Directors' Guild. Credits bulletin., 1943.; 1 item. Printed. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Screen Writers' Guild., 1936-1947.; 100 items. (Box 94, Folder 8-10)
      Includes correspondence, annual report, contract negotiation demands, bulletins, by-laws.
    - Shorthand notes., 51 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Snyder's Cafe., 1938-1939.; 3 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 12)
      Financial statements.
    - Stock company. Cast list., n.d.; 3 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Studio pass., n.d.; 1 piece. (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Sturges Engineering Company. Wilmington, California
    - Accounts receivable., July 2, 1945.; 1 piece. Typescript carbon. (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Aircraft manufacturers list., n.d.; 2 pieces. Mimeograph. (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Blueprints. For airplane engine., 1936.; 5 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Brochures and clippings. v.p. Correspondence., v.d.; 30 pieces. (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - A - E. v.p., v.d.; 41 pieces. Typescript and Typescript carbon. (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Caverly, Leroy E., 1935-1942.; 129 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - F - L. v.p., v.d.; 73 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - M - P. v.p., v.d.; 45 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Rainey, L.W. v.p., v.d. 1936-1942.; 89 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - S - Z. v.p. Diesel engines., v.d.; 34 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Blueprints., 1937-1939.; 4 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Automotive engine, display stand, generator.
    - Correspondence. v.p., v.d.; 24 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Diagram. Ailsa Craig 12-16 diesel engine., n.d.; 1 piece. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Diagram. Throttle control diesel engine for yacht., 1935.; 1 piece. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - History of the Sturges Diesel Engine by Edwin Gillette. Diesel engines., April 1942.; 46 leaves. Typescript. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - History of the Sturges Diesel Engine by Edwin Gillette., 1942.; 4 copies. Typescript carbon. (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Notes., ca. 1932.; 22 pieces. Holograph. (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Report. Investigation Concerning Diesel Engines. Charles Hills Company., 1932.; 2 items. Typescript. With invoice. (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Duplex diesel engine. Report. Information Relative to the Sturges Duplex Diesel Engine., April 1942.; 2 copies. Mimeograph. (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Financial statements., 1942.; 30 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Insurance., 1949-1952.; 12 pieces. Typescript and typescript carbon. (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Invoices., 1942.; 4 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Notes., v.d.; 7 pieces. Holograph and typescript. (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Patents. Includes correspondence, claims, petition for power of attorney and patent information., 1933-1944.; 32 pieces. (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Patent Reprints
    - Cinematograph mechanism. no.1,479,888. C.B. Bowell., January 8, 1924.; 8 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Cinematographic apparatus. no.691,493. A. Rosenberg., January 21, 1902.; 5 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Cinematographic mechanism. no.1,992,706. P. Lira., February 26, 1935; 10 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Cinematographic mechanism. no.2,021,560. P. Lira., November 19, 1935.; 11 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Consecutive view apparatus. no.629,582. J. Mason., July 25, 1899.; 7 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Device adapted to maintain for a predetermined period of time a continuously moving band, film, or the life opposite a stationary body. no.1,567,746. A. Michetti., December 29, 1925.; 2 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Film feeding mechanism. no.2,122,946. P. Lira., July 5, 1938.; 7 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Kinetographic camera. no.587,729. L. Grubman., August 10, 1897.; 3 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Kinetographic camera. no.629,063. H. Casler., July 18, 1899.; 6 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Kinetoscope. no.1,045,905. C.B. Stilwell., December 3, 1912.; 3 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Means for reproducing sound and motion in synchronism. no.1,713,503. F. Von Madalen., May 14, 1929.; 10 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Picture projecting machine. no.1,427,575. J.W. and K.S. Brenkert., August 29, 1922.; 5 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Printing machine. no.738,527. T. Cossar., September 8, 1903.; 5 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Printing press. no.702,546. A.E. Dowell., June 17, 1902.; 4 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Projecting apparatus. no.704,449. R.H. Edwards., July 8, 1902.; 7 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Web feeding rolls. no.889,746. H.F. Bechman., June 2, 1908.; 3 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Web looping mechanism. no.811,270. H.F. Bechman., January 30, 1906.; 3 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Web looping mechanism for printing presses. no.501,456. J.L. Cox., July 11, 1893.; 4 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Web or film feeding mechanism, no.1,043,275. J. Urie., November 5, 1912.; 4 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Shipbuilding companies., n.d.; 1 piece. Mimeograph with holograph notes. (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Sketches and diagrams. n.p., 16 pieces. Holograph. (Box 96, Folder 21)
      Includes notebook with notes and sketches.
  - Three Times the Hour. Brock Pemberton Production
    - Reviews., ca. 1931.; 8 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Telegrams sent by Preston Sturges to cast., August 25, 1931.; 2 pieces. Typescript. (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Toy models. v.p., v.d.; 21 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 24)
      Includes brochures and correspondence.
    - X-rays., 1933.; 5 pieces. (Box 96, Folder 25)
      Sturges' personal x-rays.
  - A
    - A - Al., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences., 15 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Am - An., 11 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - American Dramatists., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - American Dramatists., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - American Dramatists., 11 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Angel, Heather., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Ap - Az., 7 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Authors' League of America., 10 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Authors' League of America., 9 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - B
    - B - Bal., 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Balcon, Michael., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Bam - Baz., 12 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Barnes, Howard and Betty., 14 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Bea - Bem., 9 pieces. (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Beahan, Charles., 1 piece. (Box 97, Folder 16)